unscramble.net 2014-09-15

# Word Unscrambler - Anagram Solver

**Privacy Statement**

**Unscramble.Net** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Unscramble.net ](http://www.unscramble.net/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site **.** ** **We will not give or sell your individual IP information to any outside company** or entity for its use in marketing or solicitation.** We may disclose this information to any third party if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such preservation or disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with legal process (b) enforce the Terms of Use (c) respond to claims that any Content violated the rights of third parties (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of unscramble.net, its members and the public.

**Cookies**

Portions of the Unscramble.net site use cookies to help personalize your online experience and to make site navigation easier. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this site.

None of the cookies gather any personal information or are used in any way to track or log a user's visit or to gather any information on their web surfing habits. Cookies may also be through our ad company or affiliate program.

See Advertisers information below.

####  Advertisers 

We have contracted with ValueClick and Google among others (known as Advertisers) to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Advertisers may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick or Google , please see their privacy policies at [ www.valueclickmedia.com ](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/about/privacy)and [www.google.com ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/)

#### Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and/or postal address). 

The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary. ****We will not give or sell your registration information to any outside company** for its use in marketing or solicitation. **We may disclose this information to any third party if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such preservation or disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with legal process (b) enforce the Terms of Use (c) respond to claims that any Content violated the rights of third parties (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Unscramble.net, its members and the public.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Unscramble.net** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us . 

Please email your request to [ privacy@unscramble.net ](mailto:privacy@unscramble.net)

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

Please email your request to [ privacy@unscramble.net ](mailto:privacy@unscramble.net)

####  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [ privacy@unscramble.net](mailto:privacy@unscramble.net)
